translia.com 2011-12-31

# Privacy Policy | Translia

Last updated on January 22nd, 2010 

This privacy policy outlines how Translia uses and protects any information that you provide us when utilizing the website.

Translia is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should Translia request you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, please rest assured that such information will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

### What Translia Collects

The specific information Translia collects from may vary, depending on how and when you use the site. Generally Translia may collect the following information:

  * Name, Job Title, Company
  * Contact information including email address
  * Third parties’ email address when you use our referral service to invite them visit our website
  * Demographic information such as postcode, Preferences and Interests
  * Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

### How Translia Uses the Information

Translia requires the information to understand your needs and to provide you with a better, more useful service.  
Translia may use the information to improve our products and services.  
Translia may send newsletters to you if you register for the newsletter or indicate interest in a newsletter. You may unsubscribe by clicking on the unsubscribe tab located in every email correspondence.  
Translia may contact you by email, phone, fax or postal mail regarding the topic(s) on which you have expressed interest in while interacting with the website.  
Translia may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.  
Translia may also use the information for internal record keeping.

### Security

We are committed to securing your information. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, Translia has put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information collected online.

### Invite a Friend

If you feel that the services of translia.com could be useful for a third party you know (e.g. your friends or family members etc), you may use our referral service. If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s email address. We will automatically send your friend a one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site.

### How Translia Uses Cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes, and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any personal information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us.

You can choose either to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting so as to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

This privacy policy covers the use of cookies by Translia and does not cover the use of cookies or other tracking technologies by any of its advertisers.

### Links to Other Websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that Translia has no control whatsoever over those other websites. Therefore, Translia cannot be held responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide while visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

Translia reserves the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our website.

### Widget

This site uses the “Share This” widget where personal information is collected in the form of the invite-a-friend feature. This feature is used to send a one time invite to the third party email address you entered through the widget. The personal information entered on this widget is subject to the privacy policy of the “Share This” widget. Rubicon Project shares no responsibility in regards to the personal information entered through the widget.

### Controlling Personal Information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways: (I) whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, make certain that it is acceptable to you with the way the information may be used before you provide it. (II) If you have agreed for Translia to use your personal information for any purposes, you may change your mind at any time by unsubscribing. Should you encounter difficulty in unsubscribing, simply contact us via email or postal mail (see contact information below) and we will assist you as soon as possible.

Translia will not sell, distribute or lease your personal information to third parties unless authorized by you or legally required to do so. Translia may use your personal information to send you promotional information about third parties which Translia think you may find interesting but only with your consent.

If you believe that any information Translia is holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us and we will promptly make the necessary corrections.

If you use bulletin board or forums this website, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

### Third Party Advertising

Advertisements that appear on Translia are sometimes delivered or served directly to Users by third party advertisers. They automatically receive your IP address when this happens. These third party advertisers may also download cookies to your computer, or use other technologies such as JavaScript and web beacons commonly referred to as “clear gifs” to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. Doing this allows the advertising network to recognize your computer each time they send you an advertisement in order to measure the effectiveness of their ads and to personalize advertising content. In this way, they may compile information about where individuals using your computer or browser saw their advertisements and determine which advertisements are clicked. Translia does not have access to nor control of the cookies that may be placed by the third party advertisers. Third party advertisers have no access to your contact information stored on Translia unless you choose to share it with them.

### Changing or Removing Information

Access and control over most personal information on Translia is readily available via the profile editing tools. Translia Users may modify or delete any of their profile information at any time by logging into their account and updating it as necessary. Information will be updated immediately. Users who wish to terminate their Translia account may send a termination message to us and all information within the account will be deleted from server. However, your communication with other Translia users and the messages you previously sent to them cannot be removed.

### Changes to the Privacy Policy

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time by updating this page. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. You should check this page periodically. Your continued use of the Translia website after Translia revises this Policy signifies your acceptance of the revised Policy.

### TRUSTe

Acosys Ltd is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent, organization whose mission is to build user’s trust and confidence in the Internet by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the Web site [www.translia.com](http://www.translia.com/ "www.translia.com"). Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to your privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe.

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact Acosys Ltd at:

  * translia at acosys dot com

Or send us a postal mail to the followings address: 

Acosys Limited  
11/F, AXA Centre,  
151 Gloucester Road,  
Hong Kong
